原料放映出品
瓦莱莉的奇妙七日
VALERIE AND HER WEEK OF WONDERS
字幕翻译制作：大傅
谁在那儿？
Who's there?
黄鼠狼！
Polecat!
瓦莱莉
Valerie.
原谅我吧
forgive me.
她的耳环呢？
Where are her earrings?
-说！  -我弄丢了 治安官
-Speak!  -I lost them, Constable.
你撒谎 奥利库 你是逃不掉惩罚的
You're lying, Eaglet. You won't escape punishment.
我要用水刑拷问你！
I'll put you to the water torture!
奥利库！
Eaglet!
弯腰 我要跳到你的背上
Bend over so I can jump on your back.
快点
Hurry up...
捣蛋鬼
you brat.
祖母 剧团来了
Grandma, the actors have arrived.
你更应该关心 传教士们要来了
You should be more interested in the missionaries arriving.
什么时候？
When?
今天或明天
Today or tomorrow.
他们其中一个 会住在我们家
One of them will stay with us.
用餐不要玩儿耳环 孩子
Are you playing with your earring, child?
我不再是孩子了
I'm not a child anymore.
其实 昨晚...
In fact, just last night...
都是在13岁...
At the age of 13...
和你妈妈一样
just like your mother.
我警告你
I'm warning you.
别碰那耳环
Get rid of those earrings.
你母亲 在进修道院那天 丢弃了它们
Your mother put them away the day she entered the convent.
你的父亲是主教
Your father was the bishop.
你知道 他们现在都在天堂
As you know,they're both in heaven now.
耳环里藏着什么秘密吗？
Is there some secret in these earrings?
噢 没有
Oh, no.
我从某个治安官手里买这房子的时候
I got them at the auction of this house
得到的这副耳环
from a certain Constable.
你认识他吗？
You knew him?
祖母 是剧团！
Grandma, it's the actors!
不 是一场婚礼
No, that's a wedding.
海德维卡结婚了
Hedvika's getting married.
求主垂怜
Kyrie ele son.
主啊 降福于她
Lord, have mercy on her.
愿她出离愤怒...
Deliver her from thy wrath...
可怜的海德维卡
Poor Hedvika.
可怜？
Why?
她已经成为地主的妻子了
She'll be a rich landowner's wife now.
祖母！
Grandma!
妖怪！
A monster!
不可能是他
It can't be him.
他早就死了
He's dead, after all.
你在说谁，祖母？
Who are you talking about,Grandma?
去练你的钢琴吧
Go practice your scales.
是 祖母
Yes, Grandma.
“美丽的少女...
“Beautiful maiden...
是我偷了你的耳环
it was who stole your earrings
又将它们送回你手中
and then returned them into your hands.
我的叔父 治安官 一直觊觎耳环
My uncle, the Constable,longs to seize them.
他杀了我的父亲和母亲
He killed my father and mother,
如今 他害怕的是你
and now fear for your fate.
今天 在教堂
In church today —
今天在教堂 将举行少女训诫会
In church today there will be a sermon for young maidens.
请将你的衣裙 挂在凉亭里
Please leave a dress of yours for me in the arbor
以便我伪装 去教堂找你说话
that might disguise myself and speak to you in church.
你可怜的奥利库”
Your poor Eaglet.”
瓦莱莉！
Valerie!
你在哪呢 孩子？
Where are you, child?
是时候换衣服去教堂了
It's time to dress for church.
祖母 我能带一小支迷迭香吗？
Grandma, may I bring a sprig of rosemary?
我 上帝的仆人
I, a servant of the Lord...
传教士
and a missionary...
今天 我来到你们中间 亲爱的少女们
have come among you today,dear maidens...
给你们阐释 启迪你们
for your instruction and edification.
哦 贞洁的少女
o virginal maiden...
知道你们是什么吗？
do you know what you are?
你们是用来敬贺的雪白的玉手
You're an alabaster hand proffered in greeting.
你们是未绽开的石榴
You're a pomegranate yet to be split open.
你们是微合的嫩叶
You're a boat-shaped leaf,
是渐开的玫瑰花蕾
an opening rosebud.
那冰冷的手
The callous hand
或将碰触你们的胸
that would touch your breast
那将留下不可磨灭的印迹
would leave an indelible imprint.
但是我与你同在，我的少女们
But I am here with you,my maiden.
在守护天使之所
In place of your guardian angel,
我向你们致意...
I bend down to you...
用最精致的油膏致意
and with the most exquisite ointment
祝福你们的唇 你们的胸...
I bless your lips,your breasts...
你们的腰
your loins.
奥利库
Eaglet.
瓦莱莉
Valerie...
真的是你吗？
is it really you?
是那怪物把我弄成这样的
That monster tortured me.
瓦莱莉 我想给你一些忠告
Valerie, I want to give you some advice.
-我们这是在广场上  -原谅我
-We're in the town square.  -Forgive me.
不要看
Hide your eyes.
好了吗？
Now?
好了
Now!
我在这儿
Here I am.
首先...
First of all...
教众们的济贫院怎么走 我的好孩子？
Where is the parish poorhouse,dear child?
在那边 神父
Over there, Father.
你是个充满仁慈的好孩子
You're performing an act of mercy.
或许你会介意给我指路？
Or perhaps you mind taking me there?
不介意 神父
Not at all, Father.
我以主的名义 向您祈求！
In God's name, I beg of you!
你先进去
You go in first.
继续走 不要怕
Go on. Don't be afraid.
欢迎光临
Welcome.
这是我的王国
This is my kingdom.
瓦莱莉
Valerie...
靠近些
come closer.
近些
Closer.
然后 你就会看到
Come and you will see.
看
Look.
不！
No!
我知道你不再爱我了 我的葛拉西安
I know that you love me no longer, my Gracián.
一晃五年了 记得你上一次在这里...
Just five years ago,when you were last here...
却如今！
but now!
走开吧 你！
Away with you!
我要鞭挞己身！
I'll whip myself!
祖母！
Grandma!
继续看
Keep watching.
这只是一个梦
This is only a dream.
我睡着了
I'm asleep...
这一切 都是梦
and all this is a dream.
他伤害你了吗？
Did he hurt you?
没
No.
他想让你爱他
He wants you to love him.
当我怕他的时候 如何能爱他呢？
How can I love him when I'm afraid of him?
这正是关键之所在
That's exactly why.
奥利库！
Eaglet!
我正等着你呢 治安官
I'm waiting for you,Constable.
多管闲事！
Damned meddler!
举起手 不然我开枪了 贼人！
Hands up or I'll shoot, thief!
爱丽莎
Elsa...
是我啊
it's me.
你认不出我了？
Do you not recognize me?
理查德！
Richard!
好久好久没有人这样 叫我的
It's been so long since anyone called me
这个名字了
by that name.
你怎么来了 理查德？
Why have you come, Richard?
我想你了
I missed you.
自从那日 你诱奸并抛弃了我...
Since the day you seduced and abandoned me...
之后我再也没有爱上别人
I've never loved another man.
呜呼哀哉
How sad.
你已人老珠黄了 爱丽莎！
How old you are now, Elsa!
不再是当年十七岁的妙龄
You were 17 back then.
要我怎样 才能像你一样返老还童！
What I'd give to become young again like you!
理查德
Richard...
告诉我你的秘密
tell me your secret.
你想要什么 我都给你！
I'll give you anything you want!
我想要回这所房子
Give me back this house.
这等于抢夺了瓦莱莉的房子
That would be robbing Valerie.
那你就准备坦白你的恶行吧
You're ready to commit far worse acts.
你说什么我都答应
I'll do anything you say.
好啊
Good.
那我们来签个小小的契约吧
Let's draw up a little contract.
你将会再次拥有青春和美貌
You will be young and beautiful again.
就在今夜
It will happen tonight,
在那个吝啬地主的婚礼上
at that miserly landowner's wedding.
你这个魔鬼！
You're the devil!
这枚珍珠会搭救你
This pearl will save you.
奥利库 瓦莱莉在哪？
Eaglet, where's Valerie?
-我把她带走了  -带哪了？
-I carried her off.  -To where?
教堂塔楼
The church tower.
过来 你这个蠢蛋！
Come here, you fool!
你也带我去塔楼！
You will take me there too!
祷告吧
Let us pray.
听到了吗？
Hear that?
钟声响三通 而后 又回归平静
Three times now the bells have begun ringing and then gone silent.
太好吃了
This is excellent.
困苦会使人的食欲大增
Hardship always leaves one with an appetite,
对此 我深有感受
and I experienced a good many things
当我去食人族中布道的时候
on my mission among the cannibals.
我救了一个黑人女孩儿
We saved a young black woman.
她非常漂亮
She was very beautiful.
她后来怎么样了 神父？
What became of her, Father?
我们把她带回帐篷
We took her to our tent
说服她信上帝
and converted her to our faith.
她非常有天赋
She showed great talent.
她成为修女了吗？
Did she become a nun?
没有 非常可惜
No, unfortunately.
她在法国港口走丢了
We lost her in a French port.
玛莎 酒呢？
Marta, where's the wine?
我会告诉你她后来怎么样的
One day I'll tell you what became of her.
她堕入淫邪之路
She fell into immoral ways
犯了第六诫 不可奸淫
and sinned against the sixth commandment.
在这方面 我会跟你好好说说的 亲爱的孩子
I'll give you a talk on the subject, dear child.
谢谢你 神父
Thank you, Father.
你的主教父亲 是个有修养 敏锐的人
Your father,the bishop,was a refined and sensitive man.
行淫者来向他告解的时候 他会昏厥
He'd faint when the prostitutes came to confession,
而所有美丽的女人都爱慕他
and all the beautiful women adored him.
我会找时间跟你多聊聊这些
I'll tell you more some other time.
他有几个孩子？
How many children did he have?
有你
He had you...
还有一个男孩 叫 奥利库
and a boy named Eaglet.
奥利库？
Eaglet?
你怎么了？
What is it?
我有点头疼 我能去躺会儿吗？
I have a headache. May I go lie down?
-晚餐还没有结束呢  -对不起
-Dinner's not over yet.  -Forgive me.
你要和我们碰杯吗？
Will you toast with us?
我从不喝酒
I've never had wine.
今天可以例外
Today will be an exception.
以纪念死去的主教
In memory of the late bishop.
奥利库！
Eaglet!
我来找你聊聊 亲爱的孩子
I've come to speak with you,dear child.
现在吗 神父？
Now, Father?
现在是最适合静思的时间啊
There is no better time for contemplation.
你的胸真美啊！
What beautiful breasts you have!
请您走开 神父！
Please go away, Father!
我渴求的是你的甜蜜
What I desire from you is sweet.
你太可爱了
You're so lovely.
-如此的高贵  -走开！
-You're magnificent.  -Go away!
让人销魂！
You're ravishing!
放开我 你这个懦夫！
I'll fight you off, you coward!
我要用死 给你良心的谴责
My death will be on your conscience.
你做了什么？
What have you done?
是鸡瘟！
The fowl plague!
鸡瘟降临了！
The fowl plague is here!
签好了
It is done.
我的房子又是你的了
My house is yours again.
现在 我们只等午夜...
And now we will wait until midnight...
在婚床边
by the conjugal bed.
来
Come.
是时候了
It is time.
我所有的梦想都碎了
All my dreams have come to nothing.
来 是时候了
Come. It is time.
我老了
I am old.
我也会老的
I shall grow old too.
-你爱我吗？  -爱
-Do you love me?  -Yes.
一滴血也没有
Not a drop of blood.
不要哭
Don't cry.
当你哭时会显得苍老
You look old when you cry.
奥利库！
Eaglet!
给
Here.
-不要这样看我  -怎样？
-Don't look at me like that.  -Like what?
跪下
Kneel down.
跪下！
Kneel down!
-冷吗？  -不冷
-Is it too cold?  -No.
我好像盲人
I'm like a blind man.
我家有一间客房空着
There's an empty guest room at our house.
你可以在那休息
You can rest there.
那个混蛋把我推下了塔楼
That bastard threw me down from the tower.
敲钟绳救了我
The clapper of the bell saved me.
嗯 我听到了反常的钟响
I heard it toll very oddly.
为你祈祷来着
I prayed for you.
鸡瘟来的正是时候
The plague is our best friend.
没有了新鲜的血 我的治安官叔叔
Without enough fresh blood,my uncle the Constable
-会像动物一样死去  -你真冷酷！
-will die like an animal.  -You're so cruel!
几百岁的他早该死了
He's been ripe for death for a hundred years,
怪物
the monster.
没什么 只是一个挂在窗户上的男人
It's nothing. Just a man hanging from the window.
我们这是在哪啊？
Where are we?
就在你的房子下面
Still right under your house.
我害怕
I'm afraid.
勇敢点
Be brave.
这些棺材里都是什么人？
Who's inside these coffins?
黄鼠狼的猎物 他们的血都被吸干了 看
Victims of the Polecat,their veins sucked dry. Look.
祖母！
Grandma!
请原谅我 不得体的着装
Forgive me.I wasn't suitably dressed.
这就是你的房间
This is your room.
我没想到会有人
I thought this room was empty.
我是乘长途夜车来的
I arrived on the night coach.
还认识我吗？我是你的远方表姐
Don't you recognize me? I'm a distant cousin.
我是爱莎
Call me Elsa.
瓦莱莉
Valerie.
这是...我的兄长
And this is... my brother.
奥利库
Eaglet.
看样子 是我占了
I've taken your room...
你的房间
it would seem.
这里挺适合你的
You're welcome to it.
不 不可以 再给我找一间 可以吗？
No, I couldn't.You'll find me another, won't you?
我要问问祖母
I'll ask Grandma.
你的祖母出远门了 亲爱的孩子
Your grandma has gone away,dear child.
告别都没有就走了？
Without saying good-bye?
老年人经常会有古怪的心血来潮
Old people have their odd whims.
但是 我觉得你会同意我住她的房间的
But I'm sure you'll allow me to stay in her quarters.
非常乐意
With pleasure.
那 这个房间 就是你的了
This room is yours, then.
请吧
Here you are.
好想去骑马啊
I'd love to go for a horse ride.
我的马可以给你骑
I'll lend you my horse.
我很累 我要去休息了
I'm very tired.I'm going to lie down.
你真的不认识我吗？
You really don't recognize me?
不
No.
你并不怕我 对吗？
You're not afraid of me,are you?
但是自从见到我 亲爱的 你还有...
But these are silly questions, my dear...
一些傻傻的疑惑
since we only just met.
我的耳环！
My earrings!
你妹妹还没有回来？
Your sister still hasn't returned?
瓦莱莉在哪？你肯定知道
Where's Valerie? You must know.
你生气的样子可爱极了
You're adorable when you're angry.
瓦莱莉在哪？
Where's Valerie?
我可以告诉你 但有一个条件
I'll tell you on one condition.
你必须和我做爱
You must make love to me.
不可能！
Never!
那你滚出去
Leave this room.
不
No.
我又不是你的客人 该你滚！
I'm not your guest here.You leave!
你会后悔的
You'll regret this.
你会死的非常体面的
You will die a glorious death!
去死吧 瓦莱莉！
Die, Valerie!
去死吧！
Die!
奥利库！
Eaglet!
晚安了 我的黑发女孩儿
Good niqht, my dark-haired girl
晚安 做个甜蜜的梦
Good night and sweet dreams
当你醒来
When you wake
爱人啊
My love
要守护好你的秘密
Do not reveal your secret
瓦莱莉 你得救了
Valerie, you're saved.
我什么都听到了
I heard everything.
我表姐爱上你了
My cousin's in love with you.
-你表姐？ -我知道
-Your cousin?  -I know.
她就是祖母
She is Grandma.
她偷了我的耳环
She stole my earrings.
但那耳环是空的
But they were empty.
耳环的真正秘密 在此
Here lies their secret.
它们会保护你远离危险
They'll protect you from mortal danger.
要提防黄鼠狼
Beware of the Polecat.
他在哪？
Where is he?
-他要死了  -可怜的
-He's dying.  -Poor thing.
他蛊惑了你
He's bewitched you.
瓦莱莉
Valerie...
我爱你
I love you.
不 不行！ 我们是兄妹！
No, you mustn't! We're brother and sister!
-主教也是你的父亲  -这不是真的！
-The bishop was our father.  -That's not true!
回来！
Come back!
瓦莱莉！黄鼠狼才是我的父亲
Valerie! The Polecat is my father!
我会 我不会
I will, I will not
我会！
I will!
我要死了！
I'm dying!
现在你知道 老是什么滋味了吧
Now you know what it's like to be old.
你不用白费口舌了
You're wasting your breath.
瓦莱莉也要死了
Valerie's dying.
为了我的青春 我牺牲了她
I sacrificed her for my youth.
你终将会死 像我一样
You're doomed just like me.
你也会经历这般的抽搐
You'll suffer the same convulsions.
只有你的孙女 可以拯救我们
Only your granddaughter could have saved us both,
因为他流着我的血
because she has my blood.
怎么可能？她的父亲是主教
How could that be? Her father was the bishop.
我就是主教！
I was the bishop!
我是瓦莱莉的父亲！
I'm Valerie's father!
你撒谎
You're lying.
喝的！
Something to drink!
不准！
No!
先告诉我 如何延续我的青春
First tell me how to prolong my youth.
救瓦莱莉
Save Valerie.
她的血里藏着 我们的得救法门
In her blood lies our salvation.
瓦莱莉
Valerie.
讨厌的瓦莱莉！
Cursed Valerie!
是我
It's me...
父亲
Father.
我的孩子
My child.
来
Here.
不 这令我作呕！
No, it's too disgusting!
我又重回人身了
I'm just a man again,
我难逃一死
and I must die.
不 你不会死
No, you won't die.
你救了我
You saved me.
父亲！
Father!
-放开我！  -我又回复魔鬼身了！
-Let me go! -I'm a monster again!
放开我！
Let me go!
别碰我！
Leave me alone!
不！
No!
格拉西恩！
Gracian!
我的格拉西恩！
My Gracian!
你的爱人睡得沉如朽木
Your lover is sleeping like a log.
格拉西恩！
Gracián.
可怜的格拉西恩！
Poor Gracián.
我有个主意 爱莎
I have a plan, Elsa.
我需要奥利库的心
I need Eaglet's heart.
你要杀了奥利库？
You mean to kill Eaglet?
他的心能使我的女儿复生 并使她的永远年轻
His heart will revive my daughter and give her eternal youth.
理查德 将奥利库的心移植给我吧
Richard, transplant Eaglet's heart into my breast.
你想背叛瓦莱莉
You're betraying Valerie.
理查德 你会照我说的做的
Richard, you'll do as I say.
用血淋淋的心
With a bleeding heart.
奥利库
Eaglet...
我为什么会舍弃你？
why did I abandon you?
救命！
Help!
你的鬼魂为什么缠着我不放 瓦莱莉？
Why do you haunt me, Valerie?
不要怕
Don't be afraid.
我没死 你也还活着
I'm not dead,and neither are you.
来 我带你出去
Come.I'll lead you out of here.
沿着这条路就到教区了 神父
The rectory is across the way, Father.
是你勾引我犯罪 邪恶的女孩！
You tempted me to sin,wicked girl!
你会受到惩罚的
You will get your due.
“瓦莱莉
“Valerie.
我要说再见了
this is good-bye.
你抛弃了我
You abandoned me,
魔鬼亵渎了你的唇
and that monster defiled your lips.
我们本该幸福的在一起
We could have been so happy together
相信我 瓦莱莉
Trust me, Valerie.
黄鼠狼不是你的父亲 也不是我的父亲
the Polecat is neither your father nor mine.
你延续了他的命
You've prolonged his life.
我想成为你的守护者 朋友甚至丈夫 但是太迟了
I wanted to be your protector, friend,and husband, but it's too late.
再会了 瓦莱莉
Farewell, Valerie.
你的奥利库
Your Eaglet.”
瓦莱莉 怎么了？来
Valerie, what's wrong? Come.
海德维卡！
Hedvika!
海德维卡
Hedvika.
你怎么了？
What's wrong?
自结婚起 我日渐消瘦
I've been wasting away since my wedding day.
-你得多吃点  -不
-You must eat hearty soups.  -No.
我被吸血鬼控制了
I'm in a vampire's power.
瓦莱莉
Valerie...
看我的肩头
look at my shoulder.
疼吗？
Does it hurt?
不疼
No.
-你注意我的嘴唇了吗？  -没有 怎么了？
-You notice anything about my lips?  -No. Why?
我的嘴不脏吗？
Aren't they stained?
你肯定是吃了浆果
You've been eating berries.
和你在一起 我什么都不怕
When you're with me,I'm not afraid of anything.
我很开心
I'm so happy.
我从来都没有亲近的女友
I've never had a close girlfriend.
瓦莱莉 我得救了！
Valerie, I'm saved!
看 咬痕消失了
Look. The marks are gone.
你得吻让我恢复了健康
Your kisses have restored my health.
你真美
You're so beautiful.
有一个巫女生活在你们当中
There's a witch living among you.
她用淫言秽语折磨我
She tormented me with her sinful words.
她用嘴唇讨好我 亲蚀我
She pressed her fawning hips against me.
当她发现 我勇敢的抵挡住了她的诱惑
When she saw that I could bravely resist her temptations,
她就想用绳套勒死我
she threw a noose around my neck.
感谢上帝 我安全的逃了出来
I thank God that I escaped safe and sound.
但是那个巫女
But that witch
就藏在你们当中！
is now hiding among you!
把她交出来！她必须承受火刑！
Hand her over! She must burn at the stake!
他说谎！不要信他！
That's a lie! Don't believe him!
巫女在这儿呢！
There's the witch now!
不要信他的话！ 我发誓 他在说谎！
Don't believe him! I swear he's lying!
滚开 撒旦！
Begone, Satan!
抓住她！绑到柱子上！
Seize her! To the stake with her!
承认你是巫女吧！
Confess that you're a witch!
骗子！纵火犯！
Liar! Pyromaniac!
忏悔吧！
Repent!
长着歪毛胡子的小丑！
Hairy-faced clown!
奥利库 为何弃我于不顾？
Eaglet, why hast thou forsaken me?
她来了！ 多美啊！
Here she Is! She's lovely!
我们的主人们 旅途归来
Our masters,back from their travels,
将先出他们的手 他的脚
will give us their hands and feet.
他们的脑袋要休息
They will rest their heads,
我们将献上我们的吻
and we will kiss them.
到这来 你们这些娼妇！
Come here, you trollops!
你想要挨揍吗？
You ever had a good thrashing?
畜生！
Beast!
干了这杯酒 理查德
Drink deeply, Richard.
他死了！
He's gone!
是黄鼠狼！
The Polecat!
愿魔咒得破
May the power of these spells be broken.
晚安了 我的黑发女孩儿
Good niqht, my dark-haired girl
晚安 做个美梦
Good night and sweet dreams
当你醒来 我的爱人
When you wake, my love
要守护好你的秘密
Do not reveal your secret
祖母！
Grandma!
你去哪了？
Where were you?
你觉得呢 孩子？ 我去教堂了啊
Where do you think, child? I was at church.
传教士们都走了？
Have the missionaries gone?
什么传教士？
What missionaries?
你怎么了 我的孩子？
What's the matter, my child?
没什么 祖母
Nothing, Grandma.
祖母？
Grandma?
外面有个怪人
There's a strange man outside.
只是一个在镇上转悠的戏子
That's just one of the actors wandering around the town.
我 最亲爱的
My dearest...
不要去剧院
do not go to the theater.
相反
Instead..
即刻跃上马背
have the horses hitched up at once
奔向蓝湖
and drive to the Blue Lake.
别开枪 上帝啊！
Don't shoot, for God's sake!
不！
No!
小姐！
Miss!
你祖母不行了！
Your grandma is dying!
祖母！
Grandma!
最亲爱的祖母 你怎么了？
Dearest Grandma, what is it?
祖母
Grandma.
镜子
The mirror.
无人驾驶的马车 自己驶出了庭院
A coach with no coachman has left the courtyard.
这是个好兆头
That's a good sign.
我一直没有勇气告诉你真相
I've never had the courage to tell you the truth.
你的妈妈爱上了某个猎场守门人
Your mother loved a certain young gamekeeper.
为他生育了两个孩子
She gave him two children,
一男一女
a boy and a girl.
但是 理查德 我的情人 告诉我孩子是他的
But Richard, my lover,told me the children were his,
出于妒忌
and out of jealousy
我把你的妈妈赶出了这个家
I drove your mother from this house.
我留下了小女儿
I kept the little girl.
就是你
You are that girl.
理查德带走了奥利库 不知所踪
Richard took Eaglet away to some unknown place.
赶你妈妈出门的时候 我说
I drove your mother out with the words...
“有超一日 如果马儿
“I'll take you back
自己将你带回来 我就接受你”
when the horses bring you back on their own.”
那 我的母亲还活着？
Then my mother's still alive?
祖母！
Grandma!
母亲！
Mother!
我的孩子
My child.
这是你父亲 亲爱的
This is your father, my dear.
我好像在哪儿见过你 父亲
I've seen your face somewhere before, Father.
或许是你婴儿时的记忆
An early childhood memory,no doubt.
这一切 不会是一场梦吧？
Is all this but a dream?
但愿你的祖母能原谅我
If only your grandmother would forgive me.
晚安了 我的魔法师
Good night, my wizard
听听你的精灵 如何哭泣
Hear your fairy, how she cries
听她哭的 多么绝望
Hear her cry so hopelessly
夜晚为她抖起悲伤的披肩
The night weaves a cloak of grief for her
晚安了 我的黑发女孩儿
Good niqht, my dark-haired girl
晚安
Good night
做个美梦
And sweet dreams
当你醒来 我的爱人
When you wake, my love
千万要守好自己的秘密
Do not reveal your secret
完